const essentialsChapter15QuizData = [
  {
    question: "How are pellet stoves often vented? (Page 201)",
    options: ["Horizontal Vent installed through an exterior wall", "Factory-Built Chimney", "Through a conventional chimney", "They don't require a vent"],
    answer: "Horizontal Vent installed through an exterior wall"
  },
  {
    question: "When it comes to Pellet Stoves or Vents, you would find the clearances in the manufacturer's installation instructions or the data plate. (Page 201)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True"
  },
  {
    question: "Is it alright to mix brands or type of pellet vent pipe? (Page 201)",
    options: ["Yes", "No"],
    answer: "No"
  },
  {
    question: "Pellet Appliances should not be installed in confined spaces less than _________ cubic feet. (Page 201)",
    options: ["512", "215", "125", "225"],
    answer: "512"
  },
  {
    question: "The first thing you should do when sweeping/cleaning a Pellet Stove is _________. (Page 202)",
    options: ["Disconnect the appliance from the power source", "Disconnect any connector pipe", "Remove the chimney cap", "Remove the blower"],
    answer: "Disconnect the appliance from the power source"
  },
  {
    question: "It is often preferable to sweep the connector pipe indoors. (Page 202)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False"
  },
  {
    question: "If an elbow becomes separated, they cannot be reused or reassembled and they must be replaced. (Page 202)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True"
  },
  {
    question: "Most pellet appliances rely on _________. (Page 202)",
    options: ["Electricity", "Natural Draft", "Flow", "Natural Gas or Propane"],
    answer: "Electricity"
  },
  {
    question: "For the most part, pellet stoves produce heat by _________. (Page 203)",
    options: ["Convection", "Radiation", "Conduction", "Electricity"],
	answer: "Convection",
  },
  {
    question: "Pellet stoves blow room air across a(n) _________. (Page 203)",
    options: ["Internal Heat Exchanger", "Auger", "Firepot", "Condensing Unit"],
	answer: "Internal Heat Exchanger",
  },
  {
    question: "If you do not have a copy of the manufacturer's instructions and proper training, you shouldn't attempt to service the pellet appliance. (Page 203)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
	answer: "True",
  },
  {
    question: "You should never clean the exhaust blower on a pellet stove with a small hand brush and vacuum. (Page 203)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False"
  },
  {
    question: "Before installing the blower, check and replace the _________, if needed. (Page 203)",
    options: ["Internal Heat Exchanger", "Gasket on the housing", "Pellets for the homeowner", "Flue Liner"],
	answer: "Gasket on the housing",
  },
  {
    question: "The joint where the blower is installed on a pellet stove usually must be resealed with _________. (Page 203)",
    options: ["Mortar", "Refractory Cement", "RTV Silicone", "Liquid Nail"],
	answer: "RTV Silicone",
  },
  {
    question: "Why are the exhaust ducts on a pellet stove located inside the firebox? (Page 203)",
    options: ["They transfer heat", "They provide air", "They provide pellets", "It is the only place they fit"],
	answer: "They transfer heat",
  },
  {
    question: "Cleaning the convection blower on a pellet stove is not an important step and can be skipped. (Page 204)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False"
  },
  {
    question: "Pellet vents must be sealed with _________, unless they have integrated seals. (Page 204)",
    options: ["Mortar", "Refractory Cement", "RTV Silicone", "Liquid Nail"],
	answer: "RTV Silicone",
  },
  {
    question: "If a liner is installed to vent directly through the chimney wall above the smoke chamber, the tee cover serves to seal the flue. (Page 191)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True"
  },
  {
    question: "Every time you sweep a chimney a _________ is required. (Page 204)",
    options: ["Level I", "Level II", "Level III", "Category II"],
    answer: "Level I"
  },
  {
    question: "According to the NFPA 211, chimney and venting systems should be inspected once a year and swept when necessary. (Page 205)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True"
  },
  {
    question: "After you share the report with the homeowner, if possible have them _________. (Page 205)",
    options: ["Sign the report", "Shake your hand", "Only verbally acknowledge the report", "Prove they know how to use their fireplace"],
    answer: "Sign the report"
  },
];

if (!window.quizRegistry) window.quizRegistry = {};
window.quizRegistry['Chapter 15: Sweeping Pellet Appliance Chimneys or Vents'] = essentialsChapter15QuizData;
